A Guide to the Papers of the Virginia Quarterly Review, 1925-1935
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Gayle, William 1934, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Gayley, Charles Mills 1925 July 2, 1 l. TLS, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Gee, Wilson 1926-1931, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Gibson, George D. 1934, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Gibson, Patrick A. 1927-1930, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Gilbert, Anne Kelledy 1928-1934, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Gilman, Lawrence 1925 January 16, 1 l. TLS, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Ginder, C. Richard 1935, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Ginsberg, Louis 1928-1929, 5 items. TL(carbons), Virginia Quarterly Review to Ginsberg (Box 19)
- Glasgow, Ellen 1926-1935, 36 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Glass, Carter 1932-1933, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Glass, Meta 1931, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Glenn, Garrad 1931-1935, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Glenn, Isa 1931-1932, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Godbey, Earle 1930 September 18, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Godbey (Box 19)
- Goddard, Mrs. C.F. 1931, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Goldberg, Isaac 1926, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Goldberg, Maxwell Henry 1935, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Golding, Louis 1929, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Gooch, Robert Kent 1925-1935, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Goodman, Nathan G. 1926-1935, 25 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Goodwin, Mary Frances 1933-1934, 21 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Gordon, Armistead Churchill 1925-1926, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Gordon, Don 1929-1935, 45 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Gore, Howard Mason 1927 July 5, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Gore (Box 19)
- Gorman, Herbert 1930-1931, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Gottschalk, Laura Riding 1925, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Graham, Elizabeth 1930 February 4, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Graham (Box 19)
- Graham, Frank P. 1935, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Grahame, Elspeth 1933, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Grandgent, Charles Hall 1925-1932, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Grant, Madison 1927 March 14, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Grant (Box 19)
- Graves, John Temple, II 1929-1935, 34 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Gray, Agnes Kendrick 1930-1935, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 19)
- Green, Anne 1941, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 20)
- Haardt, Sara 1926-1929, 18 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Hale, [Annette] 1932-1934, 2 items. Letters, Virginia Quarterly Review to Hale (Box 21)
- Hall, Grover C. 1925-1932, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Hall, Radclyffe 1927, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Hamilton, Anne 1931-1934, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Hamilton, Edith 1934, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Hamilton, J.G. de Roulhac 1925-1935, 117 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Hamilton, Walton H. 1933-1934, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Hampton, David B. 1929, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Hanes, Leigh B. 1925-1932, 27 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Hapgood, Norman 1925 January 13, 1 l. TLS, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Harcourt, Brace, and Co. 1925-1935, 100 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Harding, T. Swann 1929-1935, 75 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Harper, George McLean 1925-1932, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Harper and Brothers 1925-1935, 46 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Harris, Julian 1927-1934, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Harrison, Fairfax 1925, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Harrison, Henry 1925-1926, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Harriss, R.P. 1927-1930, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Harrold, Charles Frederick 1930-1935, 43 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Hart, Harris 1926-1928, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Hart, James 1927-1932, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Hartsock, Ernest 1927-1930, 25 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Harvard University Press 1927-1935, 18 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 21)
- Havens, R.D. 1928, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Hay, James, Jr. 1925, 2 items. Letters, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Hay, Sara 1930-1933, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Hayes, Joseph Huntley 1930-1934, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Heath, Monroe 1926-1931, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Heaton, Herbert 1927-1930, 25 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- [Hench], Atch[eson]1931 February 11, 1 l. Letters, Virginia Quarterly Review to Hench (Box 22)
- Henderson, Archibald 1924-1934, 104 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Henderson, Ruth Evelyn 1929-1935, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Hendrick, Burton Jesse 1934, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Henri, Robert 1924 December 22, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Henry, H.M. 1933-1934, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Hergesheimer, Joseph 1925-1929, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Herring, E. Pendleton 1927-1934, 28 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Heth, Edward Harris 1934, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Heyward, Du Bose 1925-1935, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Hibbard, Addison 1925-1932, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Hibben, Paxton [Grier] 1925 May 12, 1 l. Letter, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Hibschman, Harry 1929-1935, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Hickey, Agnes McCarthy 1927-1933, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Hicks, Margaret de Forest 1926-1936, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Hicky, Daniel Whitehead 1929-1934, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Higgins, Anthony 1929-1930, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Higgins, Frances 1926-1930, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Hight, Lewis F. 1929, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Hill, Victor 1930, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Hinga, Mary Frances 1934-1935, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Holbrook, Stewart 1933, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Holliday, Carl 1924-1934, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Holliday, Robert Cortes 1926-1930, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 22)
- Holmes, John A. 1933-1935, 45 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Holt, Felix 1926 November 10, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Holt (Box 23)
- Holt, Guy 1929, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Holt, Hamilton 1925 January 13, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Henry Holt and Co. 1927-1935, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Hoover, Calvin B. 1933-1934, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Hopkins, Gerard 1934, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Horsley, J. Shelton 1931-1934, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Houghton Mifflin Company 1927-1935, 61 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- House, Edward Mandell 1925-1931, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Howe, W.D. 1925-1926, 6 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Hoyt, Helen 1930-1934, 25 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Hubbell, Jay B. 1925-1930, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Hughes, Herbert L. 1925-1930, 23 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Hughes, Robert M. 1925-1926, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Humphrey, Mary Churchill 1926-1929, 18 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Humphreys, W[illiam]; J[ackson]1925-1934, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Humphries, Rolfe 1926-1934, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Hunt, Robert Booker 1928-1929, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Hunter, Thomas Lomax 1927-1928, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Hutchins, Robert Maynard 1931, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Huxley, Aldous 1929-1930, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Huxley, Julian 1927-1931, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- Miscellaneous H 1925-1935, ca. 500 items. Miscellaneous authors. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 23)
- International Literary Bureau 1935, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 24)
- Interracial Cooperation Commission 1929-1931, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review w/pamphlet (Box 24)
- Ireland, Tom 1935, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 24)
- Miscellaneous I 1925-1935, 20 items. Miscellaneous authors, correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review. (Box 24)
- Jackson, George Pullen 1935, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 25)
- Jacob, Cary F. 1925-1927, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 25)
- Jaffé, Louis I. 1927-1935, 100 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 25)
- Jarman, L. Wilson 1930-1931, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 25)
- Jarrell, [Randall] 1934 July 26, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Jarrell (Box 25)
- Jenkins, W. F. 1926-1929, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 25)
- Jennings, Herbert Spencer 1929, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 25)
- Johns Hopkins Press 1925-1931, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 25)
- Johnson, Allen 1926-1927, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 25)
- Johnson, Geoffrey 1928-1935, 93 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 25)
- Johnson, Gerald 1924-1935, 121 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 25)
- Johnson, H.M. 1929-1930, 22 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 25)
- Johnnson, James Weldon 1931 March 24, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 25)
- Johnson, Josephine 1925-1934, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 25)
- Johnson, Robert Underwood 1925 July 2, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 25)
- Johnson, Wingate M. 1929-1931, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 25)
- Johnston, Forney 1929, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 25)
- Johnson, Mary 1927-1935, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 25)
- Jones, Anne B. 1925-1928, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 26)
- Jones, Catesby L. 1928 July 20, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 26)
- Jones, Howard Mumford 1925-1935, 81 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 26)
- Jones, M. Ashby 1926-1934, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 26)
- Jordan, David Starr 1925, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 26)
- Jordan, Louis F. 1925-1931, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 26)
- Joseph, Nannine 1930-1934, 35 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 26)
- Josephson, Matthew 1932-1934, 26 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 26)
- Joyce, Hewitte E. 1932-1934, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 26)
- Jusserrand, Jean Jules 1930 September 24, 2 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Jusserand (Box 26)
- Miscellaneous J 1925-1935, ca. 125 items. Miscellaneous authors, correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review. (Box 26)
- Kayden, Eugene M. 1925-1935, 69 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 27)
- Kellogg, Vernon 1925, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 27)
- Kennaday and Livingston 1925-1928, 42 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 27)
- Kennedy, Charles W. 1929-1930, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 27)
- Kent, Frank Richardson 1930-1933, 22 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 27)
- Kent, Muriel 1928-1935, 25 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 27)
- Kenton, Edna 1931, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 27)
- Keyes, Michael J. 1925 May 7, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 27)
- Keynes, John Maynard 1932, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 27)
- Kilmer, Kenton 1932-1935, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 27)
- Kimball, Fiske 1925-1931, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 27)
- Kimball, Marie 1928-1932, 37 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 27)
- King, Grace 1925-1931, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 27)
- Kirstein, Lincoln 1933-1934, 19 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 27)
- Knickerbocker, William S. 1927-1935, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 27)
- Knight, Edgar, W. 1927-1933, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 27)
- Knopf, Alfred A. 1925-1935, 62 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 27)
- Knowlton, Edgar C. 1935, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 27)
- Kootz, Samuel 1930-1931, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 28)
- Koteliansky, S.S. 1926-1927, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 28)
- Krapp, George Philip 1925 January 17, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 28)
- Kreymborg, Alfred 1932, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 28)
- Kroll, Harry Harrison 1935 April 17, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Kroll (Box 28)
- Krutch, Joseph Wood 1932-1933, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 28)
- Miscellaneous K 1925-1935, ca. 150 items. Miscellaneous authors. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 28)
- Laing, G.J. 1934, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lambeth, William Alexander 1926, 2 items. Letters, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lane, James W. 1925-1935, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lanier, Alexander Sidney 1928-1932, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lankford, Menalcus 1933, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lankes, J.J. 1930-1934, 25 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lape, Fred 1931-1935, 19 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Laprade, William Thomas 1933-1935, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Larsson, Raymond Ellsworth 1933-1934, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Latané, John Holladay 1925-1931, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lathan, Robert 1927-1930, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lauck, William Jett 1925 January 21, 1 l. Letter, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Leach, Henry Goddard 1927, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lederer, Wolf A. 1935, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lee, Gerald Stanley 1930-1931, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lee, Lawrence 1925-1935, 70 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Le Gallienne, Richard 1925 February 10, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lengyel, Emil 1929, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Leitch, Mary Sinton 1925-1935, 32 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Leonard, William Ellery 1927 June 28, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Leonard (Box 29)
- Lerner, Max 1935, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lewis, Cecil Day 1935 September 23, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Lewis (Box 29)
- Lewis, Constance Deming 1936 January 18, 1 l. Letter, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lewis, Nell Battle 1925-1929, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lewis, Sinclair 1929 December 31, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Lewis (Box 29)
- Lieber, Maxim 1930-1935, ca. 150 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- J. B. Lippincott and Co. 1926-1933, 19 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lippman, Walter 1924-1935, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lipscomb, Herbert C. 1926-1927, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Litchfield, Grace Denio 1925-1935, 2 items. Letters, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Litsey, Sarah 1928-1929, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Little, Brown, and Co. 1927-1935, 40 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- O.K. Liveright 1926-1932, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Livingston, Arthur 1925-1935, 19 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lloyd, Arthur S. 1933-1934, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 29)
- Lock, D.R. 1935, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 30)
- Loewenstein, Karl 1935, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 30)
- Long, Oliver W. 1933, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 30)
- Longmans, Green, and Co. 1928-1935, 46 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 30)
- Lorimer, George Horace 1931 January 28, 2 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Lorimer (Box 30)
- Lorraine, Joseph 1926, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 30)
- Lotka, Alfred J. 1929 September 25, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Lotka (Box 30)
- Lovejoy, Arthur O. 1927-1929, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 30)
- Lovett, Edgar O. 1925-1929, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 30)
- Lowe, Robert Liddell 1927-1934, 41 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 30)
- Lubin, Isador 1933, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 30)
- Luhrs, Marie 1931-1935, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 30)
- Lumpkin, Grace 1935, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 30)
- Lunt, Dudley Cammett 1931-1932, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 30)
- Lytle, Andrew 1931-1935, 49 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 30)
- Miscellaneous L 1925-1935, ca. 200 items. Miscellaneous authors. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 30)
- Mabbott, Thomas Olive 1926-1929, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- McAfee, Helen 1925, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- McAlmon, Robert 1930, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- McBlair, Robert 1929-1932, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Robert McBride & Co. 1932-1935, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- McBryde, John M. 1928-1932, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- MacCampbell, Donald 1933-1935, 20 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- McClure, John 1929-1933, 2 items. Letters, Virginia Quarterly Review to McClure (Box 31)
- Lida McCord & Co. 1929-1931, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- McCormick, Cyrus 1933, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- McCormick, Virginia Taylor 1924-1935, 39 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- MacDermott, Clare 1926-1934, 18 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- McFall, James 1925-1934, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- McFee, William 1932, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- McGee, Sidney 1929-1931, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- McGuffey, Edward M. 1929 September 25, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to McGuffey (Box 31)
- Machen, Arthur 1925, 2 items. Letters, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- McIlvaine, Ellan 1926-1930, 23 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- McIlwaine, Henry R. 1929-1932, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- MacKaye, Percy 1925-1934, 22 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- McKnight, Floyd 1928-1929, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- MacLeish, Archibald 1935, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- McLeod, Norman 1932-1935, 5 items. Letters Virginia Quarterly Review to McLeod (Box 31)
- Macmillan Company 1925-1935, ca. 85 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Malone, Dumas 1928-1934, 31 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Malone, Kemp 1927-1930, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Manly, John Matthews 1924 March 31, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Maphis, Charles Gilbert 1926-1931, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- March, William 1930-1932, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Maring, Helen 1929-1935, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Marks, Jeannette 1925-1927, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)